Tap "Browse Brands" and search 150+ Pakistani brands.
"Browse Brands" ট্যাপ করে ১৫০+ ব্র্যান্ড search করুন।
Open a brand — here, Baroque's official store.
একটি ব্র্যান্ড খুলুন — এখানে Baroque-এর official store।
Browse its categories and pick a product you love.
category ঘুরে পছন্দের একটি পণ্য বাছুন।
Prefer the Pakistani site for real PKR (some show higher USD).
আসল PKR দামের জন্য পাকিস্তানি site বাছুন (কিছু USD-তে বেশি)।
Copy the product link and paste it into PakPoshak.
product link copy করে PakPoshak-এ paste করুন।
It reads the item and shows your estimated total in BDT.
এটি পণ্য পড়ে BDT-তে estimated total দেখায়।
Add another product, or continue to your details.
আরেকটি পণ্য যোগ করুন, বা details-এ যান।
Enter your name, WhatsApp number, and delivery address.
নাম, WhatsApp নম্বর ও ডেলিভারি ঠিকানা দিন।
Review your full order summary and the all-in total.
পুরো order summary ও সর্বমোট দাম রিভিউ করুন।
Tap Confirm & Submit — you get an Order ID to track.
Confirm & Submit চাপুন — track করার Order ID পাবেন।
Pay with bKash, Nagad, Upay or Rocket using the details shown.
bKash, Nagad, Upay বা Rocket দিয়ে পেমেন্ট করুন।
Already paid? Enter the amount, method, and TrxID.
পেমেন্ট হয়ে গেছে? amount, method ও TrxID দিন।
Upload your payment screenshot to confirm.
নিশ্চিত করতে পেমেন্ট screenshot আপলোড করুন।
Done! We only WhatsApp you if something's out of stock.
হয়ে গেল! পণ্য stock-এ না থাকলে শুধু তখনই WhatsApp করি।